Zachary Lum

3822 Highbury Way San Ramon, CA 94582 (415) 515-2972 zachary.t.lum99@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Hard-working Digital Media Art major (3.75 GPA) currently attending San Jose State University, with 5+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of curriculum development, classroom management, and field instruction skills to successfully fill your role at your company. Frequently praised as diligent by my peers, I can be relied upon to help achieve the goals of the position.

EXPERIENCE

First Chinese Baptist Church, San Francisco, CA — *Summer Day Camp Counselor*

June 2014 - July 2019

- Duration is 6 weeks every summer starting in early June to mid-Iuly.
- Organized and planned schedules for each week.
- Counseled and supervised youth campers.
- Wrote and taught a specialized curriculum that they can apply to their lives outside of camp and to broaden their views.
- Kept track of the budget for the group.
- Communicated with directors, campers, other counselors, volunteers, and parents.

First Chinese Baptist Church, San Francisco, CA — *Summer Youth Camp Counselor*

July 2019 - August 2020

- Youth Camp is a week-long summer camp for the youth.
- Mentored campers that ranged from 7th grade to high school graduates.
- Made sure they participated in all camp activities and followed camp rules.
- Supported and worked alongside with other staff members
- Attended daily meetings on time

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

Atom

Github

Brackets

Skills with Google Suite Applications & Microsoft

Wondershare Filmora

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Indesign

Adobe Premiere Pro

AWARDS

Fall 2018 Dean's Scholar

Spring 2019 Dean's Scholar

Spring 2020 Dean's Scholar

Relevant Coursework

Art 74: Intro to Digital Media

Comm 20: Public Speaking

Art 75: Intro to Digital Video

Art 101: Digital Media Art

EDUCATION

San Jose State University, San Jose, CA — Digital Media Art

August 2018- May 2022